[Kurapika] They're coming.
They are definitely coming!
[theme song playing]
DEFEND x AND x ATTACK
[narrator] September 1st.
The day Gon, Killua, Kurapika and Leorio
have chosen to reunite in Yorknew City.
And it is on this morning
that Gon and Killua
visit the bustling Yorknew marketplace.
[Gon] Wow, look at all the people!
[Killua] The whole purpose of this market
is to swindle the visitors
who’ve come for the auction.
[Gon] Wait.
So, this isn’t the auction venue?
No, of course it isn’t.
Yorknew’s “dream auction”
is held once a year
in the world’s largest auction house.
They say that tens of trillions of Jenny
exchange hands during only ten days
of official bidding.
Tens of trillions? Really?
Yeah. Something
that sells for 10,000 today
could go for a hundred million tomorrow.
Bam, instant fortune.
It’s where dreams come true.
[Gon] Wow...
[Killua] Well, anyway,
that’s a big part of the reason
why so much of the underworld auctioning
happens at the same time.
[Gon] That’s awesome!
[Killua] So hey, you think
Kurapika and Leorio are gonna show?
[Gon] They promised
they’d meet us here today,
so I’m sure they will.
[Killua] Right.
They might try to contact us, so...
Gon! You’ve really gotta get a phone!
Every Hunter needs one!
Yeah. I know...
[shop owner] Hey, welcome!
This one’s the hottest new models.
It’s ultra-thin and no bigger
than a credit card!
Plus, it has GPS,
which is great for finding people.
-[Leorio] Don't bother.
-[Gon and Killua] Huh?
The range is terrible
and it’s not even waterproof.
The only thing it’s good for
is making phone calls.
Leorio!
Hey!
Instead, I would recommend...
this Beetle 07.
It’s pretty heavy and expensive
but it can translate over 200 languages
from places all around the globe.
Wait, Really?
-Hey, get this one and I’ll get one, too!
-[Gon] Yeah!
Two of these beauties, please!
Yes sir, that’ll be 400,000.
[screams] Four hundred--
That’s highway robbery!
[Gon] Thanks, Leorio!
[Leorio]
Sure, but a 110,580 Jenny apiece?
And that’s a fair price for a new model
in this market!
[Killua] Still, you overdid it.
I’ve never seen anyone get applause
for buying a cell phone before.
-[applause]
-[Leorio whistling]
[Gon] But you really saved us.
[Leorio] That was just a taste
of what I’m capable of.
The real deals don’t really start rolling
until after the seller asks you to leave.
[overconfident laughter]
He doesn’t really strike me
as the auction-going type.
No kidding.
So. How you coming along?
What do you mean?
You’ve both been training
and getting stronger, haven’t you?
[Killua snorts]
What?
You gave the badge
back to Hisoka at Heavens Arena?!
Not to mention you were good enough
to reach the 200th floor…
Just how strong have you gotten?
[Gon] Hey. Did you learn Nen, Leorio?
You better believe I did.
That’s awesome!
Seriously?
Why the hell would I lie about that?
It’s building up a shroud of aura,
making your own life force even stronger!
[disappointed groan]
That’s Ten, actually.
One of the four major principles
for learning Nen.
What?! Are you saying there’s more to it?
I figured it’d be something like that.
[Leorio] Greed Island?
What’s that?
A legendary game.
[Gon] We're trying to get a copy
at the auction.
But why would you even want one?
I think the game
might have a clue in it
that’ll help me find my dad.
Huh? A clue hidden in some video game?
Why d’you think that?
[Gon] It’s... kind of a long story.
[Killua] Anyway, the problem’s the cost.
How much is it?
[Killua] The lowest starting bid...
is 8.9 billion.
Did you say billion?!
And how much do you have?
[sheepish chuckle]
After some bad investments
we’re down to... five million.
Okay, guys, listen up.
This event is being held at Southernbees,
the world’s finest auction house,
so that much money
won’t even cover the entry fee.
But the acquisition rank for the game
was listed as “easy”
on the Hunter website.
Really?
[Gon] Because to get your hands on a copy,
all you need is money.
[laughs] It’s like I always say,
money makes the world go round!
-[Killua] Well...
-[both] Hm?
All that really means...
is that a real treasure
can’t just be purchased.
If you can’t get one,
and pretty easily, too,
you’re not much of a Hunter.
Right, you guys?
[miffed grunts]
[Leorio snorts]
I don’t need you to tell me that.
First things first,
we need some seed money.
Something to get the ball rolling.
Let’s search for ways
we can make fast cash in Yorknew!
[Gon] Yeah!
[Killua] Simple and stupid.
He must be an Enhancer, too.
[Milluki] Dammit. What’s wrong?!
I created a complete duplicate
of the program.
So why aren’t any events being triggered?
Did Kil trick me?
No. No, there’s no way!
He doesn’t have the skills
to forge a game
and he’s definitely not stupid enough
to double cross me!
So, either he was tricked too,
or this is the real deal!
I have to know.
I’ll find out its secret,
whatever it takes…
no matter what the cost!
I’ve got 12.7 billion left.
And I’m gonna need
at least twice that amount
to guarantee a winning bid.
Dad! I want to make a deal.
Lend me 15 billion
and I’ll kill 15 people.
Got it. Bye.
[Blimp] Autopilot engaged
to Lingon Airport.
[Milluki] I think I was
about ten years old…
the last time I left the house.
[Leorio] Huh? Swap?
[Gon] What does that mean?
[computer] “Swap meet:
A gathering for the auction
and barter of objects.”
See also: Conditional Auction.
Conditional auction?
[computer] “Conditional auction:
An exchange in which the seller
specifies a non-monetary condition
and hands the item over to the first buyer
who satisfies that condition.
-Conditions, huh?
-What does that mean?
All right...
I think I get it.
So, there’s another kind of auctioning!
[cackling]
[Dalzollene] At 9:00 tonight,
the mummy of Princess Corco
will be sold off
at the Underground Auction.
Ivlenkov, Tocino and Baise,
you’ll be responsible for the bidding.
[Basho] Are three people gonna be enough?
[Dalzollene] Buyers can only enter
in groups of three.
Weapons, communication,
and recording devices
are all strictly forbidden.
The Mafia that runs
the Underground Auction
also handles security,
so there’s rarely any trouble.
All it takes is one miscalculated move
and then every Mafia member in the world
becomes your enemy.
This auction is built
on a foundation of trust.
And that’s the reason
you won’t see
any surveillance cameras on-site.
The one unspoken rule
is that any grudges
are to be checked at the door.
And so, if anything does happen,
your word is of utmost importance.
There are no courts here,
but it will hold the same weight
as sworn testimony.
It’s crucial that each one of you
makes a glowing impression.
Don’t cause minor disturbances
for any reason.
Speak to no one outside of this group.
And... The rest of us?
[Dalzollene] Basho and Linssen will be
covering the rear entrance.
Kurapika and Melody
will take the front entrance.
Squala and I will guard the girl.
And so...
the mission will now begin.
[Leorio] Step right up, folks!
Let’s have a little
conditional auctioning fun!
Here’s what’s up for bid!
A diamond worth three million!
Bought today
with a certificate of authenticity!
Arm wrestling decides the winner!
First person to beat this boy walks off
with the diamond!
Entry fee is ten thousand!
All right. The auction starts now!
-I want in on that!
-Me, too!
[man] Same here!
[Leorio] No pushing, people!
Form a line.
Adjust your strength to match
that of your opponent.
And pretend to struggle
every now and then.
-Okay, you’re up first!
-[gasps]
[Leorio] The entry fee in advance, please.
Here ya go. Ten thousand.
Thank you, sir. Now step right up!
[grunts]
[Leorio] All right, clasp hands.
Just do what I told you.
[Gon grunts]
And remember...
you get one round!
Ready... Go!
[both straining]
[Leorio] Uh-oh!
-Can he do it?
-[Gon straining]
You’re almost there.
Don’t give up now!
[fake straining]
[roaring]
[straining]
Oh! That was a close one!
Ah, dammit! I lost to a little kid!
And who will be our next contender?
Ready... and go!
[crowd cheering and hooting]
[Killua] I get it.
So, this is conditional auctioning.
But to reach 8.9 billion,
we’ll need 889,999 wins.
[man] Ah, damn.
Another loser!
So, who’s up next?
You lose!
[murmuring]
[onlooker 1] He's beaten 150 people!
[onlooker 2]
He’s gotta be running out of steam.
[onlooker 3]
He looks tired and he’s sweating bullets.
[onlooker 4]
Don’t lose before I get my turn!
[Gon] I feel bad for tricking everybody.
Making so much money this easily...
I’m breaking out in a cold sweat
just thinking about it!
Okay! So, who’s up next?
Look at that!
We have our first female challenger!
[onlooker 1] All right! Get him, girl!
[onlooker 2] And try to take it easy
on the little lady, muscle boy!
So, tell us where you’re from!
All business, I see...
-I look forward to our match.
-[Gon] Oh. Yeah, same here.
[gasps]
Ready, and... go!
[Gon and girl straining]
[Gon straining severely]
[straining]
Oh! So close! Better luck next time!
Yeah, good effort, girl!
Thank you for the opportunity.
Oh. You’re welcome. Any time.
[sighs] What a pity.
Was that... full power?
Yeah.
I wonder who she is...
[Killua]
World champion arm wrestler, maybe?
[Franklin] Well?
[girl] I lost.
He’s tough.
[Feitan] That little brat?
I sort of wanted that diamond.
Then you shoulda used your left hand.
[Feitan] Yeah, why didn’t you use
your stronger arm?
Oh. Because...
he extended his right hand first...
I think I’d like to challenge him again.
[Feitan] There is no time.
We have a job to do.
[Franklin] He’s right.
Besides, buying and bidding’s
not our style.
We’re thieves, remember?
[Feitan] If we want something, we take it.
[Neon] No way!
I'm going!
-[bawling]
-[grunts]
[Dalzollene] Hear that, Sir?
I’m at a loss here!
[Dalzollene] Yes, sir.
Her tantrum--
Her crying exhausted her.
That’s right, she’s fast asleep now, sir.
But there’s simply no telling
what we’re all in for
when she finally wakes up again.
I vow to obtain the items
she wants, but...
she’s set
on participating in the bidding herself.
She’s bound to be disappointed
when she wakes up to find
that she missed her only chance
at doing so.
[Nostrade] Very well.
I’ll adjust my schedule and head over.
For now, focus on getting
the mummy of that princess,
so we can improve her mood again.
[Dalzollene] Understood, sir.
[Dalzollene sighs]
[dialing number]
Well? How are things with you?
[Melody] All clear.
There’s Nothing from the outside.
Yes, sir.
We’ll call you if anything new happens.
[siren wailing]
[Melody]
They’re being quite thorough, aren’t they?
No one is allowed
within 500 meters of the auction house,
except for approved
Mafia security personnel.
[Kurapika] If they didn't do that,
the perimeter
would be crawling with thugs,
which would practically be an announcement
that sinister deeds are taking place.
[Melody] Guess so.
[Kurapika] I wonder...
will the Phantom Troupe really show up?
[gasps]
[Melody]
That’s the same sound I heard earlier.
Hmm?
Just so you know,
I happened to see you
as you were leaving the Hunter agency.
I heard it when you walked past me.
Your heart played a melody of wrath.
Mind if I ask you a question?
[Kurapika] Go ahead.
-Scarlet Eyes.
-[light gasp]
Exactly...
what do they mean to you?
[siren wailing]
Why do you ask?
There’s no reason in particular.
Just curious.
When you saw the image on the data card,
your heartbeat was even more fearsome
than it was then.
It played a melody of boundless fury.
I guess there’s no point in lying.
I am a member of the Kurta Clan.
Our eyes are normally brown,
but they burn a bright crimson
when we’re agitated.
So, I wear black contact lenses
to escape detection.
I seek the eyes
that were stolen from my brethren.
And whatever it takes...
I will return their eyes to them.
[Melody] Hmm...
Will you tell Dalzollene about me?
No, I won’t.
Because you’d kill me if I did.
You’re very perceptive.
A heartbeat’s always honest.
When you first began confessing,
and told me your true nature,
your heartbeat was as calm as it was icy.
The heartbeat of one who is prepared...
to kill if need be.
Your heart says you hold no grudges
but that I was fair game if I talked.
[Kurapika] Why did you take this job?
[Melody] Why would you ask?
You know that I’ll probably lie to you.
Your eyes will tell me if you do.
[Melody] I’m also a Pro Hunter.
A Music Hunter, I suppose.
I seek a certain sheet music.
[Kurapika] You aren't lying,
but you left out crucial details.
[Melody giggles]
[Melody] Let’s say you’re right
and leave it at that.
It’s the Sonata of Darkness.
That’s what I’m after.
It is said to be composed
by the devil himself.
There are solo parts for the piano,
violin, flute, and harp.
If a human plays
or even listens to the piece,
they will be horribly cursed.
Isn’t that just an urban legend?
I doubt that anything like that
could truly exist.
[wind rustles]
[Kurapika gasps]
The only solo I heard was the flute solo.
One movement turned me
into what you see now.
My friend who played it died,
and her whole body turned to this.
Just a single movement
from someone who had given warnings
never to play it under any circumstances.
That day...
we were drunk and giddy.
My body was destroyed,
but I gained this ability in return.
I wish to restore my body
to the way it was.
I’m willing to do anything.
I don’t want anyone else
to suffer the same fate as me.
That’s why I want to find the score
and destroy it.
You asked me why I took this job.
The answer is I was hoping
one devil would know another.
[sighs]
Looks like it’s time.
The Underworld Auction is about to begin.
It’s almost time.
It is.
[narrator] The Phantom Troupe prepares
to bare its fangs.
And soon Kurapika, now a bodyguard
for the Nostrade family,
must decide on how to deal with them.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Basho!
He writes a lot of haiku,
his homeland’s poetry.
-Let me do one!
-[gasps]
“This segment
is a test of heart and soul.”
You’re way off!
[Gon] Next time:
“A x Shocking x Tragedy”.
-Shocking!
-[Killua] Shocking?
[Gon and Killua] It’s a Shocker!